♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
- [Dmitri] Just because I treated you well
- [mid-tempo music playing]
doesn't mean you're the one
I want for my daughter.
He doesn't want us to be together.
Didn't Audrey object?
[Atoy] She doesn't know, Godmother.
She doesn't know yet.
You should have finished off
that Atoy long ago,
so I wouldn't be worrying now!
You keep giving me problems, Red!
[in English] Let me correct my mistake.
[Mercado] A terrorist group
known as Obsidian is reportedly training
here in the Philippines.
‪PREVIOUSLY
[receptionist, in English]
How can I help you, sir?
Sokolov.
[in English] Mr. Alexei Sokolov.
[in English] My brother, Andrei.
Andrei Sokolov.
[receptionist, in English]
Here are your access cards.
[in English] Thank you.
[Mercado] But your mission
is to retrieve a laptop containing
the location of the camps.
[Samir, in English] Stop!
[in English] What is your name?
[in English] We are the Sokolov brothers.
[in English] You are brothers?
Uh-huh.
[in English] You two?
[Atoy] Hm-mm.
[in English] Okay, brothers,
you can proceed to the waiting area.
[in English] The ambassador
is still in a meeting.
[in English] Oh.
[in English] We, uh… We are also here
for, uh, for meeting.
[in English] Yes.
[in English] You are early, sir.
[in English] Well, you know what they say,
"Early bird catches worm."
[laughing]
Uh, because worm…
- Uh, we're early, and the birds…
- [mutters]
- [indistinct chattering]
- Very good. Very good.
‪[quirky sting]
[in English] This way.
[music fades]
[in Russian] The Maldives is beautiful.
[in English] I plan to put a resort there.
[in Russian] Seriously?
[man 3, in Russian]
I was there last month.
[man 1, in English]
You're here for the meeting?
[Atoy] Hmm?
Uh…
[in English] Uh, yes, yes.
[device blips]
[in English] What business are you into?
[in English] Oh, uh…
[clicks tongue, in English] Textiles.
[device blips]
[speaking in Russian]
[in English] Thank you.
[in English] Uh… I made it myself.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] The ambassador will see
you now. Please come with me.
[speaks in Russian]
[music swells]
- [Atoy groans]
- [soft rock music playing]
Atoy, Atoy, your neck!
- Oh, it's coming off.
- [gasps]
Hey, you're right.
[Atoy muttering]
[Atoy groans]
- Okay? Is that okay?
- That's okay, oh-- [grunts]
[Samir, in English] Mr. Sokolov,
what is happening here?
[rousing music playing]
[suave theme music playing]
[music fades]
[Kurt, in English] Oh, yes?
[in English] Can I help you?
[in English] No. I should
be asking that question.
[in English] What are you doing
to your brother?
- [mutters]
- [in English] Why are you choking him?
[chuckles, in English] No, no.
[in Russian] No, no. He…
[in English] He has
a bad rash on his neck.
[in English] It's something itchy.
- [in English] Sir, are you okay?
- [Kurt] No. [stammers]
[grunts]
[in English] Sorry. I apologize.
My mistake. I--
[in English] You, my friend,
are too close.
- [in English] I will talk to your brother.
- [in English] Yes, yes, yes. Okay, yes.
- [in English] Of course, yes, yes.
- [in English] I will talk to your brother.
[in English] Very good, very-- Ah, yes.
[in English] What is happening here?
What is going on?
- [sneaky music playing]
- [Kurt mutters]
- Uh…
- [chuckles] Uh…
[in English] Is there something
wrong with your neck, sir?
[in English] No. I, uh…
I just dropped my, uh, pen.
[in English] I use it for, uh…
Yes. Itchy, itchy. Yes.
[in English] Allergy.
[in English] Okay. You two, come with me.
[Atoy, in English] No, no, no, no.
- [music fades]
- [in English] My brother will stay.
[in English] He's, um,
not feeling well. Right?
[in English] I-I will--
I will go with you.
[groans, in English] Yes.
[in English] Bad oysters
from last night. It's--
- [in English] Okay. You stay here.
- [in English] Relax, brother.
[groans]
- [in English] Come, let's go.
- [in English] Shall we?
- [in English] Yes. Follow me.
- [Kurt sighs]
[soft rock music playing]
[music fades]
[suspicious music playing]
[line ringing]
[Gavin, in English] Where's my phone?
There! [clicks tongue]
[sighs]
[music fades]
[in English] Auntie, are you okay?
[in English] No.
[in English] I'm not okay.
I haven't heard from Atoy
since our dinner here at home.
Perhaps Brother Atoy is just really busy.
Maybe he has a lot of orders at his shop.
[in English] Or he could simply
just be ghosting you.
[sinister music playing]
Why would he do that?
Atoy isn't like that.
And besides, we already have a child,
and we've built our family.
[tense music playing]
[in English] Fyodor Orlov, Mr. Ambassador.
[in English] My name is Ivan, Ivan Petrov.
[in Russian] I'm Pyotr Lebedev.
[suspicious music playing]
[Viktor, in English] You are new here.
[in English] I have not seen your face.
Uh…
[in English] Viktor Petrov,
ambassador of Zahran.
[in English] Mr. Ambassador,
I am Alexei Sokolov, sir.
[in English] Please, sit.
[Atoy sighs]
[in English] So,
you are the elder Sokolov brother?
- [in English] That's right.
- [Viktor, in English] I'm glad you came.
[in English] But, uh,
where is your brother now?
[sneaky music playing]
[gasps, in English] Yes?
Uh… I am, uh, Andrei Sokolov.
[in English] I am, uh…
I'm just getting water.
[in English] Just drinking water.
There's nothing wrong with that, huh?
[in English] Of course, sir.
Uh, is everything okay?
[in English] Uh, don't worry.
You seem a little nervous.
[in English] Just relax.
One of the Sokolovs is here.
What could he be doing?
[in English] I'm just, uh,
waiting for my brother. Hmm?
Do you understand Tagalog?
Are you really a foreigner?
[sneaky music playing]
[in English] Actually, uh, yes.
A little bit, a little bit.
Uh, uh… [sighs]
[in English] You know, it's a long story.
[in English] I was separated
from my brother when we were young,
you know, and I love him so much.
[in English] I ended up here
in the Philippines.
[in English] Oh, I thought I would
never see my brother again!
[sobs, in English] It's so sad.
[in English] But then, he found me!
[in English] And I'm so happy.
I have a brother again!
[in English] A whole family.
[laughs]
[in English] Congratulations, sir.
We are happy for you.
[chuckles, in English]
Thank you, thank you, comrades.
[in English] Okay.
[Atoy, in English] Oh, he's just outside.
[in English] Talking to some girls.
- [Viktor] Oh!
- [sneaky chuckle]
- [sneaky music playing]
- [laughs]
[in English] So, he's a ladies' man,
and you are the businessman
of the family, yes?
Ha!
[in English] I like your style.
[in English] It's very refreshing.
- [scoffs]
- [Atoy chuckles]
[in English] He is in the business
of textiles, that is why.
Ah!
[Viktor, in English] No wonder.
- [Viktor, in English] Very nice.
- [in English] Thank you.
[suspicious music playing]
- [in English] Oh
- [indistinct].
[speaking in Russian]
[Viktor, in English] Please.
- [Viktor, in English] Please sit.
- [device blips]
[clears throat]
- [blipping]
- [Mercado, in English] Oh, you found it!
That's our target.
You can really be relied on, Padua.
If you have the chance
to get it now, do it.
But make sure you won't be compromised.
[in English] No need to answer.
Just do it if you can.
[soft rock music playing]
I'LL SEE IF I CAN MOVE
TOWARDS THE OBJECTIVE NOW, SIR
Samir.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Bring this to my office.
[tense music playing]
[in Russian] Last week we were in Kazan.
[in Russian] We met with our colleagues
by the Lenin statue in Gorky Park.
- [in English] Good.
- [Russian] They're quite the characters.
[in Russian] We discussed some business.
[in Russian] But some strange things
are happening there.
[in English] Very nice.
[in English] Uh, Mr. Ambassador, uh…
[in Russian] Excuse me,
where is the restroom?
‪Ah.
[in Russian]
- [in Russian] Oh, to the right.
- [Viktor, in Russian] To the right, yes.
[in English] Thank you.
[music fades]
Where are you now, Atoy?
I'm already worried.
[pensive music playing]
[clicks tongue]
Annoying!
[tense music playing]
[device blipping]
[in English] Hey! What are you doing here?
[rock music playing]
Uh…
[in English] I-I-I look for toilet.
Toilet.
[in English] Sir, there are
no toilets here. None.
[in English] Oh, yes. Uh, I know.
[in English] I know. No, no, no toilet.
[in English] I'll go.
I cannot see a toilet here.
[in English] Sir, you are acting
very suspicious.
[in English] I will have to tell
the ambassador.
- [in English] Come on.
- [in English] Hey, hey, hey, hey!
[in English] You-You get
your hands off me!
[in English] You idiot!
Why are you holding me?
[in English] I'm just looking
for the toilet
because I'm gonna pee-pee, huh!
[in English] You--
So you cannot do that to me! I am--
[mumbling]
- [grunts]
- [Kurt panicking] Alexei!
- [in English] Brother.
- What are you doing to my brother, huh?!
- [in English] What did you do?
- [in English] Your brother is the one
- who hurt me first!
- [in English] Brother.
[in English] That man! That man
don't make me wanna go pee-pee!
[in English] Sir,
what did you do to our guest?
[in English] I did nothing to this man!
[in English] He attacked me
when I called him out!
- [Kurt, in English] He attacked you?
- [in English] Yes!
- [in English] My brother attacked you?!
- [Samir, in English] Yes.
- [in English] Look at him.
- [Atoy coughs]
[in English] He is weak, like a baby!
No, like a little girl!
[in English] He won't attack you!
He's so old.
- [coughs]
- [in English] You do not smell him now?
[in English] His breath
smells like wet dog and mothballs.
[in English] It's terrible.
All day, all night,
- I smell him. It's--
- [in English] Brother!
[in English] It's so bad! Look.
You are a liar.
- [in English] He didn't attack you! Why?
- [English] I'm not feeling well.
[in English] I want to--
[sneaky music playing]
[in English] Are you okay, Alexei?
[in English] Okay, let's go.
[music fades]
Where did this fabric come from?
There's no match.
Atoy sewed a suit last night.
Ah… Where is it?
There's no fabric like that
among the fittings.
He already used what he sewed.
He has a new mission.
[in English] Mission?
Atoy has a mission?
[sneaky music playing]
Is this it? These are the scraps
he used for his disguise in…
It's huge--
[in English] Forty-six, chest.
Fifty-one at the be--
It's huge-- Did Atoy swallow a ball?
Ah! [smirks]
I know this.
Atoy is pretending to be pregnant.
- Hmm? Isn't it?
- [quirky sting]
Only someone with a big belly
could wear this.
One with a big, big stomach.
Would a pregnant woman wear a suit?
Of course, it's Atoy!
[smirks]
He should have just brought me along.
I could easily be his assistant there.
I could pretend to be…
uh, the husband of the pregnant woman.
Yes, I'm the husband.
I'll accompany him to give birth,
- or maybe for a check-up, right?
- [Ame] No!
They might not believe
you're the father. Atoy might fail!
- [cackles]
- [quirky sting]
[in English] Wow!
- I'm so embarrassed for you, Ame! Hmm?
- [quirky sting]
[chuckles]
Move aside. I'm sweeping.
Okay. I'll move-- I'll move aside.
Mmm, hmm.
There. I'll help you.
Here's the dustpan.
- Go back to your tailoring shop!
- [chuckles]
Miss!
[in English] I'm not feeling well, uh--
- [in English] Like, I feel sick.
- [Kurt] Oh.
[in English] There is negative energy
in this office!
- [Atoy sighs]
- [man] All right.
- [inaudible]
- [in Russian] What's going on here?
- [device blips]
- Oh, oh!
[in English] Mr. Ambassador. [chuckles]
[in English] Sir, this man…
[in English] This man harassed me!
[in English] You know,
you see, I'm an old man, and I…
I… I forget where the toilet is.
[in English] Here or there, or here,
there. But he's mad at me!
[soft rock music playing]
[in Russian] I am sorry.
[in English] Really, really sorry.
- [in English] Sit, brother. Sit.
- [groaning]
[in English] So much shame.
[in English] Negative energy!
- [spits]
- [Atoy groans]
- [in English] Let's go.
[in English] Andrei, Brother,
do not leave me, Brother.
[in English] Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[in English] He was hitting me first.
- [elevator dings]
- [Atoy] Come on, come on.
- Come on, come on.
- [in English] Safe to leave?
[in English] What are we
gonna do now? What--
- What if they find out who we are?
- Anyway.
So, if there's a problem
with the elevator,
we won't get through. Let's go.
Where did you lose your ID badge, Sir Ben?
If I knew, I would have found it already.
How's that?
I can't get inside.
I still have duty the day after.
How long does it take to replace it?
[tense music playing]
But we're on rotation tomorrow.
[security guard] Never mind.
I'll just notify
my replacement at the service entrance.
[device blips]
[Ben] Okay, okay. Just make sure
the spelling is correct.
Ben Laput.
It's letter U, not letter O.
[softly] Let's go, let's go.
[Atoy] That was great, what we did.
[muffled chattering]
Oh, hey!
Where did you come from?
Why are you together?
Uh, ‘Son, I'll tell you later, okay.
Go shampoo your hair. It'll come off.
- [in English] Okay, okay.
- [Atoy] All good?
[in English] Ah, stop! Wait a minute.
[sneaky music playing]
So-- You were together on the mission?
[in English] Emerson,
you should have seen it!
[in English] It was amazing!
We almost got caught!
I was so nervous.
I didn't know if I was going to throw up
or faint from nerves.
[in English] What?
[in English] Come on!
You two, together?
Why didn't you bring me?
You, you got to join! Who are you?
[in English] Goldilocks?
Why did he get to join?
Me-- Atoy, me--
You can count on me, Atoy.
- Bring me along next time!
- [in English] Emerson, relax, relax.
I told you already.
- No!
- I told you--
- Told you?
- Next time, I'll bring you.
[mutters]
You might not bring me.
I'll bring you. Next time, promise.
- [in English] Promise, okay.
- Yes.
I got you. You and me, right?
Okay.
Thank you so much for all your help.
You were amazing.
You improvised so well earlier.
- I'm really impressed.
- [in English] Thank you, Atoy. Thank you.
I just-- I can't believe
this is your work.
Wow, it's like--
It's very impressive, but also… scary.
[in English] But I never
felt so alive before.
- [grunts]
- [Atoy] It's fine.
Just don't think about it too much.
Life goes on here in Tabang Lupa.
- [Kurt, in English] Yes.
- [in English] Secret.
[in English] I don't know, Atoy.
[in English] I don't know if I can ever
go back to normal after today, but…
[in English] I'm just happy
that I could help.
Till next time.
[Emerson] What do you mean till next time?
It's not like that, Brother Kurt.
[in English] Give chance to others!
I'm the others, oh!
[in English] Oh? Atoy, actually,
specifically, if you need, in the future,
like, uh, a white dude
or, like, a foreign guy,
uh, you just let me know.
Anything Emerson can't do, I'm there.
- [in English] You just let me know.
- [Atoy chuckles]
- [Atoy] Okay. I'll count on that.
- [Kurt] Okay.
- [in English] Thank you.
- Okay.
[sneaky music playing]
‪[quirky sting]
Emerson, okay.
Do better next time, okay.
You're in the mission.
In the frustration.
[Atoy] Here, sir, there's CCTV there.
In the other corner, there's another one.
Then here, at the south entry,
there are two guards.
Here, at the west entry,
there's one, and here,
right in front of the ambassador's office,
there are three.
[in English] I'm not shocked.
It's an embassy.
The place is certainly highly secured.
The question now is,
how do we extract the laptop?
Look at this.
[keyboard clacks]
See this window?
There's a platform outside this window.
Ben, he has access to that platform.
He's the window cleaner of the building.
My plan is, Ben will be my next identity.
If it's hard to enter the building
from the inside,
I'll do it from the outside.
How will you do that?
Sir, the building's facade is all glass.
What I'll do is make a small hole,
just enough to get in.
That's the ninth floor.
Isn't that dangerous?
You'll be exposed. Someone might see you.
[in English] I know, sir.
That's why I accepted this job,
even if it's hard.
Because our national security
will be in danger
if we don't retrieve this laptop.
[tense music playing]
[Cita mutters]
You seem to be hanging around
the tailoring shop more often.
I don't know if you
don't have customers or…
you don't have food at home?
- Hmm?
- I'm just passing the time, miss.
So I won't get bored.
And I'm also waiting for Atoy. Maybe…
he can bring me along
on his missions, his errands.
Mm-hmm. Oh, that's it.
That will be good for you.
Hm-mm.
- [knocks]
- [Cita mutters]
Hello.
[Cita] Oh. Oh. Come in, come in, come in.
- [gentle music playing]
- Um, is Atoy here?
Atoy?
Uh, do you need something from him?
Um, I've been calling him,
but he doesn't answer.
He hangs up on me.
[in English] I just want to make sure
that he's okay.
Ah!
You're just being suspicious.
Atoy is just busy.
[in English] Busy?
You mean, he's on a tracking mission?
[pensive music playing]
Uh-huh.
[sighs]
I thought something happened to him.
Um… Hi!
Um, you're the one
who picked up Ibyang the other day, right?
[music fades]
How is she?
Well, she's been crying
for several nights.
She said Atoy doesn't want her anymore.
Ibyang and I talked about it.
I can't believe it!
Because I know Atoy loves her very much.
But Ame said maybe someone
just influenced Atoy,
that's why he changed his decision.
[somber music playing]
If you can't let go of Ibyang,
I won't force you.
But we can't be together
if you can't choose our child.
[Ibyang] You chose Janine?
You won't adopt me anymore?
Is she here now?
Can I see her?
[music fades]
[Kurt, in English] I've served
so many beef stew.
[in English] Besides Atoy, I think
you're the only one
I've ever seen who does it like that.
[in English] You're almost
like brother and sister.
[Nestor] You said it, Brother Kurt!
You'd really think Atoy
is Karla's brother.
- Mm.
- They even have the same eyes.
‪UP NEXT
Just a warning.
What we're about to do is dangerous.
The national security
of our country depends on this.
We will defend the nation.
I will be a hero.
- Prepare yourself.
- Is it still him?
[Samir clicks tongue, in English]
I want you to check his profile.
[in English] His name is Alexei Sokolov.
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias